let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "A technician from your ISP has arrived to help you troubleshoot a weak WAN connection, to what location do you take her ?",
        answer: "Entrance facility",
        options: [
            "IDF",
            "Work area",
            "CEO'S office",
            "Entrance facility"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "A transceiver was recently damaged by a lightning strike during a storm. How might you decide whether the ISP is responsible for replacing this device, or whether your company must foot the bill ?",
        answer: "Look at whether the device is located on the ISPs side of the demarc",
        options: [
            "Look at whether the device is located on the ISPs side of the demarc",
            "Look at the manufacturer information on the device's label",
            "Look at purchase record for the device to determine when it was acquired",
            "Look at what kinds of cables are connected to the device"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following devices are you likely to find in the MDF ?",
        answer: "Routers,Switches,KVM switch",
        options: [
            "Routers,Switches,KVM switch",
            "Laptop,APs",
            "Network printer,workstation",
            "Dock station,cameras"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which device converts signals from a campus's analog phone equipment into IP data that can travel over the internet ?",
        answer: "VoIP gateway",
        options: [
            "VoIP PBX",
            "VoIP endpoint",
            "VoIP gateway",
            "VoIP switch"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What type of diagram shows a graphical representation of a network's wired infrastructure?",
        answer: "Wiring schematic",
        options: [
            "Rack diagram",
            "Wiring schematic",
            "Network map",
            "Network topology"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "If you are shopping for a rack switch, what component on the switch tells you it can be mounted to a rack ?",
        answer: "Rack ears",
        options: [
            "AC adapter",
            "Rack ears",
            "Padded feet",
            "Large fans"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "You need to connect a new network printer to a nearby wall jack. What kind of cable should you use ?",
        answer: "Patch cable",
        options: [
            "Fiber optic cable",
            "Patch cable",
            "Backbone cable",
            "Plenum-rated cable"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "You've decided to run an Nmap scan on your network. What app could you open to perform this task?",
        answer: "Zenmap,Command prompt,PowerShell",
        options: [
            "google,OneDrive,AWS Console",
            "Microsoft edge,google chrome",
            "Zenmap,Command prompt,PowerShell",
            "OKTA,Zscaler,vsCode"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of these is considered a secure place to store a list of documented network passwords ?",
        answer: "A password manager",
        options: [
            "The CEO's smartphone",
            "A sticky note under the keyboard",
            "A password manager",
            "The MDF"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the first step of inventory management ?",
        answer: "List all components on the network",
        options: [
            "Interview users",
            "Backup network data",
            "List an administrative account's username and password for each device on a network",
            "List all components on the network"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: " There is only one __ per network, but there can be many __ connecting internal portion of the network",
        answer: "MDF,IDF",
        options: [
            "MDF,IDF",
            "ARP,ATB",
            "BRP,BDP",
            "SMP,UDP"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Why is it important to use a structured cabling standard when installing and managing cabling systems ?",
        answer: "To maximize performance and minimize upkeep",
        options: [
            "To use cables efficiently",
            "To maximize performance and minimize upkeep",
            "To improve productivity.",
            "To have a resilient system."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Why is it important to use plenum-rated cabling in the area above the ceiling tile ?",
        answer: "Because that area of the house is usually hot so you need a cable suitable for those temperatures",
        options: [
            "Because they are very light",
            "Because of it's max length",
            "Because that area of the house is usually hot so you need a cable suitable for those temperatures",
            "Because of their weight"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What is the unit of measurement that defines the space available in a rack? ",
        answer: "Rack Units",
        options: [
            "Rack feet",
            "Rack Centimeters",
            "Rack Meters",
            "Rack Units"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Why is it important to minimize cable clutter in a rack?",
        answer: "Helps prevent airflow blockages and heat buildup",
        options: [
            "To secure the rack",
            "Helps prevent airflow blockages and heat buildup",
            "To be able to see the cables labels",
            "To make the inside of the rack more visible"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "What are some elements that are typically included in network diagrams ?",
        answer: "Switch, router, firewall, server, workstation",
        options: [
            "transceivers, crimper, tone generator, packet sniffer",
            "Switch, router, firewall, server, workstation",
            "cables, mouse, keyboard, ipad",
            "hardrive, headset, camera, phone"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "How tall are standard racks?",
        answer: "42U tall",
        options: [
            "42U tall",
            "43U tall",
            "44U tall",
            "45U tall"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "How can you go about gathering the information needed to assemble a thorough operations manual ?",
        answer: "Take some time to brainstorm all the elements you want to include in the manual and consider how you will keep each elements in the manual updated",
        options: [
            "Do some researchs on google",
            "Ask help from colleagues",
            "Take some time to brainstorm all the elements you want to include in the manual and consider how you will keep each elements in the manual updated",
            "Get an experienced network engineer to do it for you"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "For what time period should you schedule a network change?",
        answer: "Maintenance window",
        options: [
            "Office hours",
            "Holiday",
            "Weekend",
            "Maintenance window"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: " In a large organization, how do you typically request permission to perform a network change ?",
        answer: "Submit a change request document,understand and follow the approval process",
        options: [
            "Submit a change request document,understand and follow the approval process",
            "Ask to the IT manager during a meeting",
            "Talk to the CEO of the organization",
            "Make an announcement on the organization website"
        ]
    },

]